<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GetCourageNow.org - GetCourageNow.org is a non profit providing News and tools to fight Climate Change using self organising tools for Climate Change campaign organisations.</title>
    <link>https://getcouragenow.org/</link>
    <description>  A non-profit providing secure, open source, self organising software for Climate Change campaign organisations.
</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Hugo v0.59.1</generator>
    <atom:link href="https://getcouragenow.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Article - 6 Amazing Things That Will Happen If We Flip The Senate - by Gary Krane</title>
        <link>https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/article-6-amazing-things-that-will-happen-if-we-flip-the-senate-by-gary-krane.html</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[

<p>Please keep in mind that if the Dems retake the Senate, as well as the House, here are six astoundingly wonderful changes that can, and very likely, if we put sufficient pressure on the Dems, will happen:</p>

<pre><code>  ![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1540023612695-TWTC1TOVM30UE14FDIWD/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kJ6S_F8teGVt8uo2xehHOchZw-zPPgdn4jUwVcJE1ZvWQUxwkmyExglNqGp0IvTJZamWLI2zvYWH8K3-s_4yszcp2ryTI0HqTOaaUohrI8PImK3kUdDsYt0az5jlzliAA2WlMyaZYLn9P8CH6MhBKIIKMshLAGzx4R3EDFOm1kBS/6-things-image-1.jpg?format=original)
</code></pre>

<ol>
<li><p>Congress will be likely to pass Medicare for all, especially if enough American have GetCourageNow or an equally powerful mobilization and commitment tool to pressure the moderate and conservative Dems and moderate GOPers to do the right thing.</p></li>

<li><p>Congress, again given enough pressure on moderate and conservative Dems and moderate GOPers, will be able to make significant cuts in our bloated $700B+ military budget and use those funds for a Green Marshall Plan (Green New Deal) to massively accelerate our transformation to an 80- 100% renewable energy economy in the next 10-15 years, and in the process, create 10M well paying jobs.</p></li>

<li><p>Congress will be able to restore the powers and enforcement capabilities of the EPA to stop the ravaging of our public lands, rivers, aquifers and lakes, the rapid destruction of species, and the fossil fuel industry&rsquo;s rapid destruction of any livable future for humanity past 2040.</p></li>

<li><p>Congress will by Begin to significantly reduce our grotesque criminal levels of wealth inequality and wealh addiction by passing much higher tax rates on the rich, closing huge loopholes for the rich, and by using this new revenue to significantly improve our early childhood, elementary and secondary public education system, significantly reduce the cost of higher education, and provide real affordable housing, thereby increasing social mobility.</p></li>

<li><p>Establish a trifecta necessary to implement the nuclear codes that would initiate a nuclear war, ending the ability of one man, Donald Trump from doing so</p></li>

<li><p>And LAST but not Least, the Senate will be at worst only 3 votes away from what they will need in the Senate to Impeach Trump, and very likely less than that, because the &ldquo;3 votes&rdquo; figure was based on a Newsweek story a year ago, when 12 GOP Senators were identified as willing to seriously consider impeaching Trump. Given all that has since been uncovered and likely to soon be exposed by the Mueller investigation, that number might now be 16 Republican Senators, the number the Dems would need to have the <sup>2</sup>&frasl;<sub>3</sub> majority to convict.</p></li>
</ol>

<p>For all this to happen, in the neck and neck US Senate race states, it&rsquo;s not enough to vote. Download the free GetCourageNow app from GetCourageNow.org to make it easier than ever to do much more than just vote, even if you feel too busy.</p>

<h2 id="download-the-free-getcouragenow-app-to-find-local-volunteer-opportunities-that-fit-your-schedule-and-your-priorities-it-s-availible-on-the-apple-app-store-and-on-google-play">Download the free GetCourageNow app to find local volunteer opportunities that fit your schedule and your priorities. It’s availible on the Apple App Store and on Google Play.</h2>

<pre><code>  ![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1540023163876-ESS83XAY2AFSDJIZWOTI/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kMZdhK24nuiy7pDeU5QmfE7lfiSMXz2YNBs8ylwAJx2qrCLSIWAQvdC7iWmC9HNtRXCH3e9MpGhDvhq91guy70itSSBcvge6QCMNGwS9N-FH_pHgOPV6AIkk6MjJFk8smw/GetCourageNow+-+App+Store+Button270.png?format=original)




  ![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1540023178773-YZDC0V58W4AOHYLO15WO/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kMZdhK24nuiy7pDeU5QmfE7lfiSMXz2YNBs8ylwAJx2qrCLSIWAQvdC7iWmC9HNtRXCH3e9MpGhDvhq91guy70itSSBcvge6QCMNGwS9N-FH_pHgOPV6AIkk6MjJFk8smw/GetCourageNow+-+Google+Play+Button+1270.png?format=original)
</code></pre>]]></description>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/article-6-amazing-things-that-will-happen-if-we-flip-the-senate-by-gary-krane.html</guid>
      </item><item>
        <title>Article - Call to Action: Canvassing - By Gary Krane</title>
        <link>https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/for-all-those-that-say-i-care-but-i-just-dont-have-the-time.html</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[

<p>According to the October IPCC (Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change) report, their <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/07/climate/ipcc-climate-report-2040.html">latest study by 90 climate scientists, from 40 countries, analyzing 6000 studies </a>we have less than 12 years to stop using fossil fuels and switch to a solar-wind-geothermal economy before a catastrophic future. Twelve years before agriculture stops working, famines become widespread, coastal cities flood, and severe multi-year droughts become so routine and devastating that mass migration destabilizes governments. Other consequences predicted by other prestigious scientists include the increased occurrence of new, untreatable and devastating plagues, this time unlike the recent Ebola disaster, spreading to the Northern hemisphere. Further, as a result from the droughts and consequent water wars, international arms control experts predict inevitable widespread bio-chem wars or worse.</p>

<p>So for all those who say &ldquo;I care but I just don&rsquo;t have the time,&rdquo; I invite you to do this thought experiment:</p>

<pre><code>  ![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1539848275738-WQPQR9GIXWTTH0AH7SM0/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kB6N0s8PWtX2k_eW8krg04V7gQa3H78H3Y0txjaiv_0fDoOvxcdMmMKkDsyUqMSsMWxHk725yiiHCCLfrh8O1z5QPOohDIaIeljMHgDF5CVlOqpeNLcJ80NK65_fV7S1URWK2DJDpV27WG7FD5VZsfFVodF6E_6KI51EW1dNf095hdyjf10zfCEVHp52s13p8g/Canvassing-Post.jpg?format=original)
</code></pre>

<p>First consider the extra hours you are working to keep up with your overpriced healthcare costs, and if you have kids, your soon to incur higher education costs, certain to occur if we soon do not pass medicare for all and free or affordable college education.</p>

<p>When you consider these current and soon to arrive major costs, and then add onto that the much greater costs to your lives and the next generation as a result of our continued failure to address catastrophic climate change, and put this up against the fact that our best chance to  avert and begin to reverse all these terrible consequences,will depend on how Americans vote Nov 6th, merely days from now,<strong>_ how can you not make the time to get involved, to do much more than just vote?!_</strong></p>

<p>Also, if you continue to tell yourself you don&rsquo;t have time, that you have other priorities, consider the following:</p>

<p>From now to Nov 6th, You will spend on average far more hours distracted by social media posts and comments, that based on social research will lead you to be more depressed than non social media users, and  that will do nothing to avert the above impending disasters, nothing in fact to significantly enrich your life, nothing that will reduce your healthcare and education cost, than the 4-6 hrs one canvassing shift lasts, a shift that can in fact be fun (see below), great exercise,  and a great adventure, a shift that could multiply your vote several times.</p>

<p>If you are the parent who takes your kids to soccer or piano practice, you&rsquo;ll again spend more hours in a week than the 4-6hrs it takes to knock on 80-100 doors, and for the lack of a few hundred more people in your state willing to do just that, you&rsquo;re almost guaranteeing the US Senate Democratic candidate who&rsquo;s tied with the GOP candidate to lose by likely one vote per precinct (or less!)&ndash;the margin, btw, that enabled Kennedy to win in 1960, and thereby responsible in part for creating a very scary future for your soccer or piano playing kid, a planet with potential 50-70% of plant and mammal species extinct, and the wonders of nature that we older folks have had the enormous luck to experience, gone forever.</p>

<p>Finally, you also will have missed the opportunity to achieve the highest purpose (beyond food and shelter) of being a parent&ndash;the chance to imbue your kids with the most important of all values&ndash;to have the courage to stand up against injustice&ndash;by modeling that for them, by simply taking you kid(s) with you as you knock on doors, provide rides, provide supporter housing for activists willing to come from out of state who need free housing, etc and btw, when you knock on a stranger&rsquo;s door with your kid by your side, that stranger is several times more likely to open the door and actually have a polite, even life-changing, conversation with you. And if your kid is over 7, he or she might soon want to try their hand at talking, thereby developing his poise and self confidence.</p>

<p>_ - by Gary Krane co-founder of GetCourageNow  _</p>

<h2 id="start-doing-more-then-just-casting-a-vote-start-donating-your-time-download-getcouragenow-today">Start doing more then just casting a vote. Start donating your time. Download GetCourageNow today.</h2>

<pre><code>  [![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1539847840262-VAGGYWW6OON9BOK3HONV/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kMZdhK24nuiy7pDeU5QmfE7lfiSMXz2YNBs8ylwAJx2qrCLSIWAQvdC7iWmC9HNtRXCH3e9MpGhDvhq91guy70itSSBcvge6QCMNGwS9N-FH_pHgOPV6AIkk6MjJFk8smw/GetCourageNow+-+App+Store+Button270.png?format=original)](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/getcourage/id1412145042)




  [![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1539847910729-RXLA0ZK6I5D9BXWFOJMC/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kMZdhK24nuiy7pDeU5QmfE7lfiSMXz2YNBs8ylwAJx2qrCLSIWAQvdC7iWmC9HNtRXCH3e9MpGhDvhq91guy70itSSBcvge6QCMNGwS9N-FH_pHgOPV6AIkk6MjJFk8smw/GetCourageNow+-+Google+Play+Button+1270.png?format=original)](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.getcourage.getcourage)
</code></pre>]]></description>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/for-all-those-that-say-i-care-but-i-just-dont-have-the-time.html</guid>
      </item><item>
        <title>GetCourageNow Midterm Volunteer Tshirt Giveaway</title>
        <link>https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/getcourage-midterm-volunteer-tshirt-giveaway.html</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Want to put the cherry on top of that oh-so-good feeling of volunteering? Why not have that cherry be a brand new T-shirt! We are happy to say that Danny over at Blue Wave Botique has offered to support our cause the best way he can by donating 50 super soft and stylish T-shirts. Head over to <a href="https://bluewave.boutique/">Blue Wave Botique’s website</a> to check out some of the clever designs Danny has come up with.</p>

<p>From now until the end of the 2018 midterm elections we will be giving away a T-shirt to anyone who meets the following criteria:</p>

<ol>
<li><p>You must like the GetCourageNow Facebook Page.</p></li>

<li><p>You must download the GetCourageNow app.</p></li>

<li><p>You must volunteer to any of the campaigns or causes we currently have on our app.</p></li>
</ol>

<p>If you have met all these criteria we will send you an email with instructions to redeem your t-shirt.</p>

<p>Limitations: Must be 18 years or older, must be a US Citizen, one entry per person, void where prohibited.</p>]]></description>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/getcourage-midterm-volunteer-tshirt-giveaway.html</guid>
      </item><item>
        <title>Help Autumn Zemke Win Nevada AD 40</title>
        <link>https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/autumnfornevada.html</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[

<h3 id="download-our-app-today">Download our App today.</h3>

<pre><code>  [![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1539667287433-MULWSGJCQT6V3DETVCGC/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kM8gjLDDGRTmNdyX_GmpY79Zw-zPPgdn4jUwVcJE1ZvWEtT5uBSRWt4vQZAgTJucoTqqXjS3CfNDSuuf31e0tVGzqP_v8q_hAxVlCx0CTos0AJR8Srl7crQ_bAF1DdiEg8Y7NDhP2oKiM3zyEiUrQlM/GetCourageNow+-+App+Store+Button300.jpg?format=original)](https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fitunes.apple.com%2Fus%2Fapp%2FGetCourageNow%2Fid1412145042%3Fmt%3D8&amp;h=AT1oN0yXQvgbEE3zQoHYhuweRtcU-ZORcM9hH_y3LCg_u1czmZOYNr6oqsRjQjpHtXAm11zcRuGSY0MyGp45R0zc7lifivY6q26Xf6DRDtJjq2X6Av1beRE)




  [![](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1539667328496-E1BSCTB4T3XR02JNFQZG/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kM8gjLDDGRTmNdyX_GmpY79Zw-zPPgdn4jUwVcJE1ZvWEtT5uBSRWt4vQZAgTJucoTqqXjS3CfNDSuuf31e0tVGzqP_v8q_hAxVlCx0CTos0AJR8Srl7crQ_bAF1DdiEg8Y7NDhP2oKiM3zyEiUrQlM/GetCourageNow+-+Google+Play+Button+1300.jpg?format=original)](https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fplay.google.com%2Fstore%2Fapps%2Fdetails%3Fid%3Dcom.getcourage.getcourage&amp;h=AT1oN0yXQvgbEE3zQoHYhuweRtcU-ZORcM9hH_y3LCg_u1czmZOYNr6oqsRjQjpHtXAm11zcRuGSY0MyGp45R0zc7lifivY6q26Xf6DRDtJjq2X6Av1beRE)
</code></pre>

<h2 id="because-to-save-democracy-nature-and-get-real-justice-voting-is-not-enough">&ldquo;Because to save democracy, nature, and get real justice, voting is not enough&rdquo;</h2>

<hr />

<pre><code>   [caption id=&quot;&quot; align=&quot;alignnone&quot; width=&quot;2200.0&quot;]![ Easily volunteer for candidates like Jacky Rosen in Nevada who need your support. ](https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5985dfd0b8a79b27663a4a57/1539712826652-C6NMW44KQSGW06TVOHJW/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kPQxYSRa1hpRjrrvb_rUndt7gQa3H78H3Y0txjaiv_0fDoOvxcdMmMKkDsyUqMSsMWxHk725yiiHCCLfrh8O1z5QPOohDIaIeljMHgDF5CVlOqpeNLcJ80NK65_fV7S1UQBd-oF9Es8BSCQQj_Roi6g7bZlCSyromUi3Qm4Bc2JDZtJ3qR9G2BYeA0wOAaeYNg/Hand-Holding-Clean-Smartphone-Mockup.gif?format=original)  Easily volunteer for candidates like Jacky Rosen in Nevada who need your support. [/caption] 
</code></pre>

<h2 id="getcouragenow-has-partnered-with-autumn-zemke-to-help-take-back-nevada">GetCourageNow has partnered with Autumn Zemke to help take back Nevada.</h2>

<h2 id="what-is-getcouragenow-getcouragenow-is-an-app-designed-to-help-you">What is GetCourageNow? GetCourageNow is an app designed to help you:</h2>

<ul>
<li><h2 id="identify-important-campaigns-convenient-to-your-location">Identify important campaigns convenient to your location</h2></li>

<li><h2 id="let-campaigns-know-how-your-skills-can-be-helpful">Let campaigns know how your skills can be helpful</h2></li>

<li><h2 id="get-the-support-you-need-childcare-transportation-lodging-etc-to-help-out">Get the support you need (childcare, transportation, lodging, etc.) to help out</h2></li>

<li><h2 id="team-up-with-people-who-share-your-interests">Team up with people who share your interests</h2></li>
</ul>

<h2 id="and-if-you-can-t-help-directly-getcouragenow-will-provide-you-with-ways-to-support-those-who-can">&hellip;and if you can’t help directly, GetCourageNow will provide you with ways to support those who can.</h2>

<p>“In the battle between the forces of good and evil, greed and compassion, only one thing has consistently made the difference—organising”<br />
— KURT VONNEGUT</p>

<hr />]]></description>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://getcouragenow.org/2019/10/16/autumnfornevada.html</guid>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
